<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Research on Muhammad Yaseen</title>
    <link>/categories/research/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Research on Muhammad Yaseen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/research/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>An Introduction to Statistics using SPSS</title>
      <link>/myaseen208/2018-08-16-pastic-ntu/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/myaseen208/2018-08-16-pastic-ntu/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Statistics Variable Measurement Measurement Scales Descriptive Statistics Example Reference  Boxwhisker Diagram Example Reference  Scatter Plot Example Reference  Regression Analysis Simple Linear Regression Example Reference  Multiple Linear Regression Example Reference  Polynomial Regression Analysis Example Reference  Analysis of Variance (ANOVA) Example Reference Example Reference  Analysis of Covariance (ANCOVA) Example Reference Same Slopes but different Intercepts Different Intercepts and different Slopes  Factorial Experiments Example Reference    Introduction alt text</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emerging Technologies in Research: Google Apps and SPSS</title>
      <link>/myaseen208/2018-05-15-pastic-fsd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/myaseen208/2018-05-15-pastic-fsd/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Statistics Variable Measurement Measurement Scales Descriptive Statistics Example  Boxwhisker Diagram Example  Regression Analysis Simple Linear Regression Example Exercise Exercise  Multiple Linear Regression Example  Polynomial Regression Analysis Example  Analysis of Variance (ANOVA) Example Exercise  Analysis of Covariance (ANCOVA) Example Same intercepts but different slopes Different intercepts and different slopes  Correlation Analysis Simple Correlation Analysis Example  Partial Correlation Analysis Example  Multiple Correlation Analysis Example  Completely Randomized Design (CRD) Example  Randomized Complete Block Design (RCBD) Example  Latin Square Design Example    Introduction alt text</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An introduction to R for Agricultural Research</title>
      <link>/myaseen208/2018-r-aari/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/myaseen208/2018-r-aari/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Regression Analysis Simple Linear Regression Example Example Example  Multiple Linear Regression Example  Polynomial Regression Analysis Example  Analysis of Variance (ANOVA) Example Example  Analysis of Covariance (ANCOVA) Example Same intercepts but different slopes Different intercepts and different slopes  Correlation Analysis Simple Correlation Analysis Example  Partial Correlation Analysis Example  Multiple Correlation Analysis Example  Completely Randomized Design (CRD) Example  Randomized Complete Block Design (RCBD) Example  Latin Square Design Example    Introduction  R is a free, open-source programming language and software environment for statistical computing, bioinformatics, visualization and general computing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Help</title>
      <link>/myaseen208/help/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 22:13:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/myaseen208/help/</guid>
      <description>This is not a help service for all your Statistics, R, Python and/or LaTeX questions, so please don&amp;rsquo;t post questions in the comments, or send them to me by email.
If you have questions about Statistics and/or data analysis, ask for help on crossvalidated.com.
If you have questions about R, ask for help on stackoverflow.com.
If you have questions about Python, ask for help on stackoverflow.com.
If you have questions about LaTeX, ask for help on stackoverflow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About myaseen208</title>
      <link>/myaseen208/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 16:17:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/myaseen208/about/</guid>
      <description>This is my blog site where I will put my thoughts about Statistics, R, Python, LaTeX and Research.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Analysis with R: Introduction of R Language</title>
      <link>/myaseen208/2018-r-maldives/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/myaseen208/2018-r-maldives/</guid>
      <description>The Workspace Data types Vectors Matrices Lists Data Frames Reading/writing data from/to files (Import/Export Data) Connecting to the database Numerical or Graphical Summaries of data. Summarize Data Bar charts and Dot charts ggplot2 package  The mpg Data Frame Data Transformation Filter Rows with filter() Comparisons Logical Operators Missing Values Arrange Rows with arrange() Select Columns with select() Add New Variables with mutate() PakPC2017Tehsil Data Frame Scatter Plot dygraphs plotly datatable   The Workspace The workspace is your current R working environment and includes any user-defined objects (vectors, matrices, data frames, lists, functions).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>