<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Python on Muhammad Yaseen</title>
    <link>/categories/python/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Python on Muhammad Yaseen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/python/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Regression Analysis with Python</title>
      <link>/myaseen208/2018-regpython/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/myaseen208/2018-regpython/</guid>
      <description>Statistics Variable Measurement Measurement Scales Regression Analysis Simple Linear Regression Example  Multiple Linear Regression Example  Polynomial Regression Analysis Example    Statistics   Statistics is the science of uncertainty &amp;amp; variability Statistics turns data into information Data -&amp;gt; Information -&amp;gt; Knowledge -&amp;gt; Wisdom Data Driven Decisions (3Ds) Statistics is the interpretation of Science Statistics is the Art &amp;amp; Science of learning from data     Variable   Characteristic that may vary from individual to individual Height, Weight, CGPA etc     Measurement   Process of assigning numbers or labels to objects or states in accordance with logically accepted rules     Measurement Scales   Nominal Scale: Obersvations may be classified into mutually exclusive &amp;amp; exhaustive classes or categories Ordinal Scale: Obersvations may be ranked Interval Scale: Difference between obersvations is meaningful Ratio Scale: Ratio between obersvations is meaningful &amp;amp; true zero point     Regression Analysis   Quantifying dependency of a normal response on quantitative explanatory variable(s)     Figure 1: Population Regression Function    Simple Linear Regression   Quantifying dependency of a normal response on a quantitative explanatory variable    Example   Weekly Income ($) Weekly Expenditures ($)    80 70  100 65  120 90  140 95  160 110  180 115  200 120  220 140  240 155  260 150    Income = [80, 100, 120, 140, 160, 180, 200, 220, 240, 260] Expend = [70, 65, 90, 95, 110, 115, 120, 140, 155, 150] import pandas as pd df1 = pd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Help</title>
      <link>/myaseen208/help/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 22:13:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/myaseen208/help/</guid>
      <description>This is not a help service for all your Statistics, R, Python and/or LaTeX questions, so please don&amp;rsquo;t post questions in the comments, or send them to me by email.
If you have questions about Statistics and/or data analysis, ask for help on crossvalidated.com.
If you have questions about R, ask for help on stackoverflow.com.
If you have questions about Python, ask for help on stackoverflow.com.
If you have questions about LaTeX, ask for help on stackoverflow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About myaseen208</title>
      <link>/myaseen208/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 16:17:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/myaseen208/about/</guid>
      <description>This is my blog site where I will put my thoughts about Statistics, R, Python, LaTeX and Research.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>